A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade, 1994-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- II. Office of the Secretary, 2001-2006., Extent: 14.55 cubic feet (36 boxes). (Box 14, 21-55)
  - Subseries II.B. Records of Deputy Secretary Matt Erskine, 2001-2005., Extent: 8.65 cubic feet. (Box 32-52)
    - Special Projects
      - Massanutten-DPOL Regulations, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - MeadWestvaco, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Meat Inspection USDA/VDAC, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Microsoft Meeting with Steve Ballmer, 2003-2004 (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Milk Commission Consolidation, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - Missile Defense Agency, 2004-2005 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Missile Defense Agency-Victory Center, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Motorsports Initiative, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      - Nanotechnology, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Nanotechnology, 2003-2005 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Nanomanufacturing Initiative, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      - NarrowFlex-Patrick County, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      - NASA Project, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - NASCAR Hall of Fame, 2005 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - National Assocation of State Development Agencies, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - National Capitol Minority Business Group, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - National Chamber of Commerce-Trade Education Program, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - National Governors Association Prisoner Reentry Policy Academy, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - National Governors Association, Winter Meeting, 2002-2003 (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Meeting between Governor and Dr. Orji Uzor Kalu, Governor of Abia State of Nigeria, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Nestle-Danville, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 16)
      - New Millenium Studios/TV One, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      - New Town Project, Williamsburg, Virginia, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 18)
      - Nippon Wiper Blade, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 19)
      - Norfolk and Southern Heartland Corridor, 2004 (Box 45, Folder 20)
      - Norton Relay Center, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 21)
      - Occoneechee Golf Course, 2002-2004 (Box 45, Folder 22)
      - Olympic Committee Washington, D.C./Baltimore, 2002 (Box 45, Folder 23)
      - Outdoor Tourism, 2003-2004 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Outdoor/ECO Rural Tourism, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 2)
      - Outdoor/ECO Rural Tourism, 2003-2005 (Box 46, Folder 3)
      - Outdoors-Progress Fund, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      - Outdoors-Tourism and Transportation, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 5)
      - Joseph Parsi/Sister City with Rome, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 6)
      - Parkhurst (Dorothea Knitting), 2002 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - Pepsi Bottler DBA Loan-Smyth/Wythe Counties, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - Petersburg VEC Building, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - Pillowtex (Martinsville/Henry County), 2003 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Pittston Coal Layoffs, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Phillip Morris, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - Preferred Drug List (PDL) Eli Lilly, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - Press Calls and Contacts, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - Project Sunrise Proposal, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - Project-Financial Services Call Center, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Power Systems International FOIA Request, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - Questerra, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - Regional Competitiveness Act, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - Research Development Research Priorities for Budget, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - Rob Snyder, Federated IT, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - Sandy Point Tract Nature Conservancy, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Secure Virginia, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Senior Racing League, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 24)
      - Southern Governors' Association, 2004 (Box 46, Folder 25)
      - Sherwood Brands, Mecklenburg County, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 26)
      - Shipbuilding Summit, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 27)
      - Small Business Study-Best Practice Team, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI), 2003 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI), 2003 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI), 2003 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI), 2004 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI), 2004 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Small Business Initiative (SBI)-Venture Fund Idea, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Small Business Support, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Small Business Support, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Southern Growth Policies Board-Jim Clinton, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Southwest Virginia Economic Development Commission, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Southwest Virginia Economic Development, 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Southwest Virginia Mental Health Facility, Smyth County, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Space Flight Authority (Va.), 2002-2004 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Virginia Commercial Space Flight Authority, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Spirent Communications (VEDP), 2002 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Stephenson, Ned, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - State Dept. Training Facility, 2002 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - STARS Group (Statewide Agencies Radio System), 2002-2003 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Strategic Planning and Executive Agreements, 2003-2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - TechRiders, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Textile, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Tobacco Securitization, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Tracker Marine Lead, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Tennessee Valley Authority, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Tredegar-Civil War, 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Trinity Package, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Truck Driving School, Patrick County, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Unemployment Benefits (Virginia Employment Commission), 2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - United Airlines, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - U.S. Chamber of Commerce-Trade Roots Program, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - United Mine Workers of America, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - University Based Economic Development, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - University Based Economic Development Officers, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - Urban Strategy, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 15)
      - Uzbekistan Delegation Visit, 16 May 2002 (Box 49, Folder 16)
      - Virginia Association of Broadcasters, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 17)
      - Vincent, Donna, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Virginia Business Education Partnership, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 19)
      - Virginia Captial Meeting/Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 20)
      - Virginia Commonwealth University, Monroe Campus, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Corps State Council, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 22)
      - Virginia Department of Agriculture and Consumer Services, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Economic Developers Association, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 24)
      - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 25)
      - Virginia Economic Development Partnership Board Meeting Finance Committee, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 26)
      - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, Director's Compensation, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 27)
      - Virginia Economic Development Partnership, Priority Focus Areas, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 28)
      - VEDP, Tobacco and GOF, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 29)
      - Virginia Economic Resource Initiative, Enhanced Capital, HB 1322, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 30)
      - Virginia Employment Commission, Marie Cheeks, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 31)
      - Virginia Employment Commission, Mary Pudner Case, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 32)
      - Virginia Employment Commmission, Unemployment Insurance, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 33)
      - Virginia's Finest, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 34)
      - VITA Combined CATT Meeting, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 35)
      - VITA-Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 36)
      - VITA ITIB Presentation, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 37)
      - VITA-Major Projects, 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 38)
      - VITA-Sec. of Commerce and Trade Priority Projects, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 39)
      - VITA-Small Agency Consolidation, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 40)
      - VITA Technology Projects, 2003-2004 (Box 49, Folder 41)
      - VITA-Virginia Employment Commission, 2002-2004 (Box 49, Folder 42)
      - Virginia Hospitality and Travel Association, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 43)
      - Virginia Leaders in Export Trade (VALET), 2004 (Box 49, Folder 44)
      - Virginia, Maryland and D.C. Regional Collaboration, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 45)
      - Virginia Philpott Manufacturing Extension Partnership, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 46)
      - Virginia Research and Technology Advisory Commission, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 47)
      - Virginia Sustainable Future Conference, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 48)
      - Virginia Tech, 2003-2005 (Box 49, Folder 49)
      - Virginia Tech-Virginia Capital Relations, 2005 (Box 49, Folder 50)
      - Virginia Tourism, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 51)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation-African American Tourism Initiative, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 52)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation-Publication RFP, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 53)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation-Tourism Map, 2002-2003 (Box 49, Folder 54)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation-Travel South, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 55)
      - Virginia Workforce Council, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 56)
      - Virtual University, 2003 (Box 49, Folder 57)
      - Volvo Truck, Pulaski, 2002 (Box 49, Folder 58)
      - Hunter Watson, Poplar Hill, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - Wine, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - Wine, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - Wine, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - Wine Board, 2004-2005 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Wine Tourism Signage, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - Women Owned Business Council, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Town of Woodstock, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - World Trade Organization Subsidies Update, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Workforce Academy, National Governors Association, 2002-2003 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Workforce Academy, National Governors Association, 2003 (Box 50, Folder 11)
      - Workforce Bills, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Workforce Career Development Report, 2003 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Workforce-Demand Plan Jobs Equilibrium, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Workforce Development, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Workforce Investment Act, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Workforce Investment Act/Workforce Investment Board, 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Workforce-Reengineering One Stop Center, 2002-2003 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Workforce Training, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Events
      - Governor's AG Marketer Awards, Richmond, 12 February 2002 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Hiden America Inc., South Boston, 15 February 2002 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Strayer University, Henrico Campus, 6 March 2002 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Virginia Food and Beverage Expo, Richmond, 20 March 2002 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Fredericksburg Regional Alliance, Fredericksburg, 27 March 2002 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - West Piedmont Business Development Center, Martinsville, 4 April 2002 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Panel Discussion, Leadership Fairfax Class 2002, 11 April 2002 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Pulaski County Economic Development Summit, 29 April 2002 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Small Business Administration Virginia Lenders Conference, 14-17 May 2002 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - James City County Celebration of Industry (Business Appreciation Week), 15 May 2002 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Small Grain Association, Warsaw, 23 May 2002 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Dahlgran Naval Warfare Center Tour, 5 June 2002 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Community Screening of Minority Report, Gloucester County, 20 June 2002 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - ATandT Wireless, Russell County, 15 July 2002 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Governor's Work Preparedness Summer Youth Institute, Virginia State University, Richmond, 29 July-2 August 2002 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - VALET Program Luncheon (Virginia Leaders in Export Trade), Richmond, 30 July 2002 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Southwest Virginia Trip, Roanoke, 26 August 2002 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Alfa Laval Grand Opening, Henrico County, 27 August 2002 (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Business Lunch, Tazewell County, 19 September 2002 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Alleghany Highlands, Alleghany County, 25 September 2002 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Open House Meadow Croft Farm, Swoope, 26 September 2002 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Red Oak E-Commerce Solutions, Mecklenburg County, 10 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Dupont's James River Logistics Center, Chesterfield County, 17 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 23)
      - Virginia Film Festival, Charlottesville, 24 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 24)
      - Employer Advisory Committee, Williamsburg, 24 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 25)
      - Professional Construction Educators Conference, Richmond, 26 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 26)
      - National Council for Continuing Education and Training, Richmond, 29 October 2002 (Box 52, Folder 27)
      - Loudoun County Economic Development Commission, Sterling, 1 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 28)
      - Dry Well Replacement Program Announcement, 7 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 29)
      - Japan Virginia Society, Consul General of Japan, Richmond, 7 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 30)
      - 1000 Job Day, Southwest Virginia, 13 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 31)
      - Tidewater Community College-Strategic Community College of the 21st Century, 13 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 32)
      - Governor's Latino Summit, 19 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 33)
      - Safecard ID Inc., Virginia Beach, 21 November 2002 (Box 52, Folder 34)
      - Department of Forestry, Charlottesville, 8 January 2003 (Box 52, Folder 35)
      - Hungarian Ambassador Dinner, Richmond, 24 January 2003 (Box 52, Folder 36)
      - Northern Virginia Coalition of Chambers, Reston, 29 January 2003 (Box 52, Folder 37)
      - VALET Orientation (Virginia Leaders in Export Trade), Richmond, 30 January 2003 (Box 52, Folder 38)
      - Launch of the Genesis Project, Richmond, 3 February 2003 (Box 52, Folder 39)
      - Southside of the James Attractions, Wakefield, 11 February 2003 (Box 52, Folder 40)
      - Gods and Generals Movie Premiere, 18 February 2003 (Box 52, Folder 41)
      - lake County Advanced Knowledge Center, Soutside Virginia, 4 March 2003 (Box 52, Folder 42)
      - Spirit of Norfolk Ceremony, Norfolk, 12 March 2003 (Box 52, Folder 43)
      - General Assembly Wrap-up: The Business Community Impact, Williamsburg, 19 March 2003 (Box 52, Folder 44)
      - HUDD Distribution Announcement, Chesapeake, 19 March 2003 (Box 52, Folder 45)
      - Virginia Employment Commission Agency Awards Program, Richmond, 20 March 2003 (Box 52, Folder 46)
      - Augusta Lumber Announcement, King William County, 8 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 47)
      - Institute for Advanced Learning Research, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, 10 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 48)
      - Cendant Corporation Grand Opening, Virginia Beach, 24 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 49)
      - Governor's Tourism Conference, Richmond, 27 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 50)
      - Governor's Higher Education Research Summit, Newport News, 1 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 51)
      - $-H Event, Richmond, 9 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 52)
      - Business Appreciation Week Kickoff, Richmond, 12 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 53)
      - Norfolk Business Apprecation Breakfast, 13 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 54)
      - Orange County Business Appreciation Reception, 14 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 55)
      - Poquoson Business Appreciation Lunch, 14 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 56)
      - Danville Business Appreciation Dinner, Pittsylvania County, 15 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 57)
      - Powhatan Business Appreciation Week, 15 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 58)
      - Kazakhstan Offical Visit Luncheon, Richmond, 20 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 59)
      - Prince William Business Appreciation Week, Manassas, 22 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 60)
      - Prince William County Economic Development Council, 22 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 61)
      - Manassas Mainstreet Kickoff, 29 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 62)
      - Hardestry Farm, Clarke County, 30 May 2003 (Box 52, Folder 63)
      - Virginia's Economic Development Plan, Reedville, 21 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 64)
      - Portfolio Recovery Associates, Hampton, 29 April 2003 (Box 52, Folder 65)
      - Sister City-Taiwan, 10 June 2003 (Box 52, Folder 66)
      - Virginia Wine Day on Capitol Hill Luncheon, Washington, D.C., 17 June 2003 (Box 52, Folder 67)
      - Virginia Electronic Commerce Technology Center, Hampton Roads, 19 June 2003 (Box 52, Folder 68)
      - BIO 2003 Convention Reception, Mount Vernon, 21 June 2003 (Box 52, Folder 69)
      - Care Rehab and Orthopedic Products, Inc., Charlotte County, 23 June 2003 (Box 52, Folder 70)
      - Charlottesville Area School Business Alliance, 10 July 2003 (Box 52, Folder 71)
      - Eli Lilly Groundbreaking, Prince William County, 17 July 2003 (Box 52, Folder 72)
      - Virginia Leaders in Export Trade (VALET) Program, Richmond, 30 July 2003 (Box 52, Folder 73)
      - Virginia Agribusiness, Lynchburg, 10 September 2003 (Box 52, Folder 74)
      - Virginia Biotechnology Summit, Tysons Corner, 13-15 October 2003 (Box 52, Folder 75)
      - Virginia Film Festival, Charlottesville, 23-26 October 2003 (Box 52, Folder 76)
      - Virginia Professional Firefighters Assocation, Richmond, 14 November 2003 (did not attend) (Box 52, Folder 77)
      - Shrader Bridgeport Check Presentation, Campbell County, 19 November 2003 (Box 52, Folder 78)
      - Line of Fire Screening, Richmond, 1 December 2003 (Box 52, Folder 79)
      - Governor's Wine Study Group, Charlottesville, 3 December 2003 (Box 52, Folder 80)
      - Wine America Dinner, Charlottesville, 3 December 2003 (Box 52, Folder 81)
      - Virginia Arts Festival, Hampton Roads, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 82)
      - Virginia Argiculture Summit, Charlottesville, 24 February 2004 (Box 52, Folder 83)
      - New Kent Forestry Center, 26 February 2004 (Box 52, Folder 84)
      - Virginia Main Street Award Luncheon, Richmond, 26 February 2004 (Box 52, Folder 85)
      - CSX Parks for Growth Events, Southampton County, 29 February 2004 (Box 52, Folder 86)
      - General Assembly Wrap-up: Commerce in the Commonwealth, Richmond, 24 March 2004 (Box 52, Folder 87)
      - StarTek, Lynchburg, 31 March 2004 (Box 52, Folder 88)
      - Virginia Travel and Governor's Tourism Conference, 25 April 2004 (Box 52, Folder 89)
      - Virginia Business Council, Arlington, 10 May 2004 (Box 52, Folder 90)
      - Riverstone Technology Park, Halifax County, 12 May 2004 (Box 52, Folder 91)
      - Degussa Goldschmidt Chemical Corporation, Hopewell, 13 May 2004 (Box 52, Folder 92)
      - Business Appreciation Week, Brunswick (Box 52, Folder 93)
      - Lynchburg Business Appreciation Week Luncheon, 19 May 2004 (Box 52, Folder 94)
      - Governor's Cup Wine Competition Award Ceremony, 3 June 2004 (Box 52, Folder 95)
      - DMME/Mineral Extraction Operations in SW Virginia, 21-23 June 2004 (Box 52, Folder 96)
      - Virginia Economic Bridge Workforce Showcase, 14 July 2004 (Box 52, Folder 97)
      - VALET Luncheon Program, 27 July 2004 (Box 52, Folder 98)
      - Metalsa Expansion Grand Opening, Botetourt County, 3 August 2004 (Box 52, Folder 99)
      - Virginia Main Street Harrisonburg Designation Event, 24 August 2004 (Box 52, Folder 100)
      - Saxon Capital Mortgage Announcement, 1 September 2004 (Box 52, Folder 101)
      - Virginia Dept. of Business Alliance, 15 September 2004 (Box 52, Folder 102)
      - Sara Lee Coffee and Tea Grand Opening, Suffolk, 17 September 2004 (Box 52, Folder 103)
      - Universal Food and Beverage Company, Inc., Grayson County, 22 September 2004 (Box 52, Folder 104)
      - Arkay Packaging Expansion Announcement, 20 December 2004 (Box 52, Folder 105)
      - VALET Luncheon, 27 January 2005 (Box 52, Folder 106)
      - NASCAR Hall of Fame Bid, 2 February 2005 (Box 52, Folder 107)
      - Tajikistan Ambassador, 3 March 2005 (Box 52, Folder 108)
      - Telvista VA Main Street Annual Awards, 30 March 2005 (Box 52, Folder 109)
      - Telvista Dedication Event, Danville, 20 April 2005 (Box 52, Folder 110)
      - Virginia Tourism Corporation Conference, 26 April 2005 (Box 52, Folder 111)
      - Tourism Cares, Mount Vernon, 12 May 2005 (Box 52, Folder 112)
      - American Woodmark Corporation, Winchester, 1 August 2005 (Box 52, Folder 113)
      - Paris Ceramics Announcement Event, Farmville, 19 September 2005 (Box 52, Folder 114)
  - Subseries II.C. Records of John Sternlicht, 2003-2005., Extent: 0.35 cubic feet. (Box 53)
    This subseries is housed in 1 box and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Records document the special projects of John Sternlicht.
    - Special Projects
      - Accelerating Innovation Foundation Conference, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Accelerating Innovation Conference (confirmation), 2005 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Doubling Net Receipts in Virginia Agriculture, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - IP Commercialization Loan Fund (Legislation, SB640), 2004 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Session (Legislative) Highlights, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Subseries II.D. Records of Special Assistant Sarah Cohn, 2002-2005., Extent: 0.70 cubic feet. (Box 54-55)
    This subseries is housed in 2 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by subject. Subjects include: Agriculture and Forestry Expo Task Force and Virginia Works.
    - Special Projects
      - Agency Issues/Events, 2004-2005 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Agriculture and Forestry Expo Task Force, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Agriculture and Forestry Expo Task Force, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Agriculture and Forestry Expo Task Force, 2003-2004 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Analysis of Nursing Programs and of Nursing School Retention in the Shenandoah Valley and Southside Virginia, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Bank Tellers and Switchboard Operators, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Forest Industry Initiatives, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - Globalization in Virginia, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Globalization in Virginia, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Hungarian Technology Center, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Intellectual Property, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Intellectual Property, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Manufacturing, 2003 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Manufacturing, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Model Legislation, 2003-2004 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - New Economy, 2002-2003 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Small Business, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - State and Local Government Conflict of Interest Training, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - SWAM, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Works, 2004-2005 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Works Correspondence, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Works E-mail, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - World Trade Organization, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- III. Budget and Legislative Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.80 cubic feet (4 boxes). (Box 56-59)
  Contains budget and legislative records created and maintained by the Office of the Secretary of Commerce and Trade. Series is arranged into two subseries. Subseries have been designated for Budget Files and Legislative Files. Original order and titles of the files were maintained. This series contains budget documents, correspondence, e-mail, briefings, legislation, notes, presentations, plans and reports.
  - Subseries III.A. Budget Files, 2002-2005., Extent: 1.35 cubic feet. (Box 56-58)